MatchSeniors Privacy Policy
===========================

Effective Date: June 18, 2024

This Privacy Policy explains how ConversionSquared Corporation ("ConversionSquared", "we", "us", or "our") collects, uses, and shares your personal information when you use our website and services. Your privacy is important to us, and we are committed to protecting your personal data in accordance with applicable laws and regulations. This policy outlines the types of personal information we collect, the reasons we collect it, how we process and share it, and the rights you have regarding your personal information.

MatchSeniors is a property of Conversion Squared Corporation (Conversion Squared). Your services are provided by Conversion Squared, who acts as a data controller for your information, as defined under the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and UK data protection laws.

Conversion Squared values our users' privacy and the protection of their data, and we build our services and operate our business with this in mind. We maintain the confidentiality of your information using advanced security technologies and robust anonymization techniques. Any shared data will be anonymized to prevent re-identification, ensuring your privacy is protected. We regularly audit our anonymization processes to comply with the highest standards. We will only process your data in accordance with GDPR and other applicable data protection laws. This privacy policy may be modified in the future, and any updates will be posted on our website.

Our website and services are not intended for anyone under 18. We do not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under 18 years of age. If you are under 18, do not use or provide any information on this website or on or through any of its features/register on the website, do not use any of the interactive or public features of this website or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, email address, or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 18 years of age, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 18 years of age, please contact us at [request@conversionsquared.com](mailto:request@conversionsquared.com)

How do we collect your information?

You directly provide Conversion Squared with most of the data we collect. We collect and process data when you:

* Register online for any of our products and/or services
* Provide your information voluntarily on one of our websites

Our company may also receive additional identifiers indirectly via your browser, such as device information, referrer information and/or geo-location data.

What information do we collect?

Certain parts of our services may ask you to provide personal information voluntarily; for example, we may ask you to provide your contact details, gender, the type of person you may wish to connect with, the area you live in, and other information.

Some of the information you provide may include sensitive personal information, such as race, ethnicity, or sexual preferences (such as whether you are looking for a male or female to connect with).

Types of personal information we collect from you voluntarily may include:

E-mail address First Name or Usernames Date of Birth or Age Gender Sexual Preferences Ethnicity Location Income

Other identifiers may include: Device Information (e.g. device model, operating system version, device date/time, unique mobile identifiers, mobile network information, IP address) Referrer information Geolocation, including IP addresses or longitude/latitude coordinates provided by your web browser

Legal Basis for Processing and Purpose of Data Collection

The information you share is used and shared with third parties for the purposes of marketing, data enrichment, and determining which of our third-party clients' services best suit you. This includes sharing data with partners who may use the information to improve their products, services, and marketing operations. This processing is necessary for the performance of a contract with you or to take steps before entering a contract, which is essential for the legitimate interests of our business. By using our services, you consent to such data sharing.

We process your data based on your consent when you opt-in to receive special offers, new products, services, promotions, and other similar information.

In addition to the information we collect directly from you, we also monitor and track usage of our website, viewing and traffic patterns, customer behaviour, and other similar information. We use this information to improve our website, product and service offerings, operations, and customer service.

Data Storage and Security

Conversion Squared uses industry-standard encryption technologies to send and receive consumer data from our site. We have appropriate technical and organizational security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

Data Retention

We will keep your personal information for no longer than necessary. The length of time we retain this information will depend on our legal obligations, the nature of the personal data shared, or our legitimate interests as a business.

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, this information will be deleted or anonymized. Please contact us using the information in the "How to contact us" section if you require additional details on the specific retention period for your personal data.

Sharing Your Information With Third Parties

We work with third parties to help with many aspects of our business, including sharing information with you, supporting you, preventing fraud, protecting our infrastructure, and providing a better experience for you. By using our services, we may share your personal data with the following categories of recipients:

* Marketing & advertising partners and analytics providers
* Law enforcement bodies, regulators, government agencies, or courts when required by law or to protect our legal rights and user safety
* Actual or potential buyers (and their agents and advisers) in connection with an actual or proposed purchase, merger, or acquisition of any part of our business

If the ownership of our business changes, we may transfer your information to the new owner so they can continue to operate ConversionSquared or its properties and provide services.

Some of our advertising partners may deploy their own tracking or cookies not administered by us. These technologies are subject to our advertisers' Privacy Policies.

Below is a list of the key third parties we work with. We may work with third parties not listed below or stop working with the third parties listed below.

* Google Analytics
* Gmail
* Hotjar
* IPQualityScore
* Kochava
* Match
* Match Affinity Group
* Mate1 Social Enterprises Inc
* McAfee
* Meetic
* Menthoda
* Optimizely
* RSVP
* Spark Networks
* The Dating Company LLC
* VWO

If you would like more information about third parties that we work with, further details may be provided on request.

Marketing & Internet Advertising

With your consent, we may share your personal information, including your name, email address, and other identifiers, with third-party partners. These partners may use this data to enrich their databases, improve their services, and enhance our marketing strategies. We ensure that any data sharing is conducted in compliance with applicable laws and regulations. If you do not want us to share your personal information with other companies or organizations, please let us know by writing to us at the above address or sending us an email message to [request@conversionsquared.com](mailto:request@conversionsquared.com). Please include your email address and the words "opt-out" in the subject or content field so that we can process your request promptly. We may also provide aggregate information about site usage and traffic patterns, stripped of any individual identification, to third parties to comply with various reporting obligations and for business or marketing purposes.

The Digital Advertising Alliance ("DAA") has made available for consumers tools on which you can register your choices not to be tracked by participating advertising networks or companies in the collection and use of your online activities. These are (1) The DAA Consumer Choice Page for Mobile Web (at [https://www.aboutads.info/choices](https://www.aboutads.info/choices)) and (2) DAA AppChoices (at [https://www.aboutads.info/appchoices](https://www.aboutads.info/appchoices)), which is a mobile app that allows you to opt-out of the collection and use of cross-app data, other than for permitted purposes, by listed third-party AppChoices participants.

You can also prevent your receipt of interest-based ads on websites by deleting and declining cookies in your browser(s). Note that your opt-out choice is applied only to the browser from which you make the choice.

Some newer mobile device operating systems allow you to limit the use of information to deliver interest-based advertising in mobile applications, or your mobile web browser may provide a "Do Not Track" browser setting which will notify those ad servers and networks who recognize the signals to refrain from sending you interest-based ads to your mobile device. You can check the settings on your device for such options in your device's operating system. Alternatively, you may wish to download the TrustE mobile application and/or the Digital Alliance "App Choices" mobile application and follow the instructions provided.

International Data Transfers: Your personal information may be transferred to and processed in countries other than the country in which you are resident. These countries may have data protection laws that are different from the laws of your country.

Specifically, our website servers are located in the USA, and our group companies and third-party service providers and partners operate around the world. This means that when we collect your personal information, we may process it in any of these countries.

However, we have taken appropriate safeguards to require that your personal information will remain protected in accordance with this Privacy Notice. We use Standard Contractual Clauses and adhere to the adequacy decisions by the European Commission to ensure a high level of protection for your data during international transfers.

We have implemented similar appropriate safeguards with our third-party service providers and partners, and further details can be provided upon request.

Keeping your information secure

Information you provide to us is stored on servers owned and operated by Amazon Web Services, Inc. More details about this provider are available at [https://aws.amazon.com](https://aws.amazon.com/). We use many best-practice security measures to keep this data safe, including private networking, firewalling, role-based access controls, authentication, backups, and monitoring. When your data is moved off of our servers for any reason, we leverage the best means available to us to make sure your data is secure in transit.

What are your data protection rights (EEA)?

ConversionSquared would like to ensure you are fully aware of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following: The right to access: You have the right to request our company for copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.

The right to rectification: You have the right to request that our company corrects any information that you believe may be inaccurate. You also have the right to request our company to complete the information you believe is incomplete.

The right to erasure: You have the right to request that our company erase your personal data, under certain conditions.

The right to restrict processing: You have the right to object to our company's processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.

The right to data portability: You have the right to request that our company transfer the data we have collected to another organization or directly by you, under certain conditions.

If you make a request, we have 30 days to respond to you. We may request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity or to exercise any of your other rights. This is a security measure to ensure that your personal data is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it. We may also contact you to ask you for further information in relation to your request to speed up our response. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us at the following link: [https://privacyportal-cdn.onetrust.com/dsarwebform/e9d6bf36-ae33-444b-a38e-d622d39ea5d5/1c41c1db-af67-49c5-b8a0-e0e3ddd135ac.html](https://privacyportal-cdn.onetrust.com/dsarwebform/e9d6bf36-ae33-444b-a38e-d622d39ea5d5/1c41c1db-af67-49c5-b8a0-e0e3ddd135ac.html) Or write to us at [request@conversionsquared.com](mailto:request@conversionsquared.com).

Your California Privacy Rights
------------------------------

If you are a resident of the State of California and would like to know how your personal information is shared with third parties by us, what categories of personal information that we may have shared with third parties as well as the name of those third parties, please contact us at [request@conversionsquared.com](mailto:request@conversionsquared.com)

Please be advised that where California residents opt-out from permitting their personal information to be shared, such individuals may still receive selected offers directly from us, in accordance with applicable law.

Subject to certain exceptions, you have the right to make the following requests:

Right to Access: You have the right that we disclose to you what personally identifiable information we have collected about you over the past 12 months. Once we receive and confirm the validity of your request, we will disclose to you:

The categories of personal information collected

The specific pieces of personal information we collected from you

The categories of third parties with whom we have disclosed or shared that personal information

The categories of personal information that we have sold (if any)

Right to Delete: You have the right to request that we delete your personal information and direct any third parties we have provided your personal information to delete your personal information. Once we receive and confirm your request, we will delete or anonymize your personal information in our records unless there are legitimate business interests in not doing so.

You may make your requests by emailing our support team at [request@conversionsquared.com](mailto:request@conversionsquared.com) or by filling out a request form here: [https://privacyportal-cdn.onetrust.com/dsarwebform/e9d6bf36-ae33-444b-a38e-d622d39ea5d5/1c41c1db-af67-49c5-b8a0-e0e3ddd135ac.html](https://privacyportal-cdn.onetrust.com/dsarwebform/e9d6bf36-ae33-444b-a38e-d622d39ea5d5/1c41c1db-af67-49c5-b8a0-e0e3ddd135ac.html)

Please allow 30 days for a response. For your protection, we may ask for proof of identity before we can answer any such requests.

Opting Out of the Sale of Personal Information

In certain jurisdictions, you may have the right to opt out of the sale of your personal information. If you wish to exercise this right, please follow the instructions below:

1. Send an email to [request@conversionsquared.com](mailto:request@conversionsquared.com) with the subject line "Opt Out of Sale of Personal Information." In the body of the email, provide your full name and email address associated with your account.

OR

3. Fill out the web form provided here: [https://privacyportal-cdn.onetrust.com/dsarwebform/e9d6bf36-ae33-444b-a38e-d622d39ea5d5/1c41c1db-af67-49c5-b8a0-e0e3ddd135ac.html](https://privacyportal-cdn.onetrust.com/dsarwebform/e9d6bf36-ae33-444b-a38e-d622d39ea5d5/1c41c1db-af67-49c5-b8a0-e0e3ddd135ac.html), and provide the necessary information to process your request.

Upon receiving your request, we will take the necessary steps to ensure that your personal information is not sold to third parties.

Please note that even after opting out of the sale of your personal information, you may still receive selected offers directly from us, in accordance with applicable law.

Cookies Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer's hard drive by our computers or servers to identify your computer. Cookies are only read by the server that placed them and are unable to execute any code or virus.

For further information, please visit [aboutcookies.org](https://aboutcookies.org/) or our own [cookie policy](https://www.matchseniors.com/cookies.php) to understand more about how we use cookies.

Privacy Policies of Other Websites/Services ConversionSquared websites contain links to other websites and services. Our privacy policy applies only to our websites, so if you click on a link to another website, you should read their privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy ConversionSquared keeps its privacy policy under regular review and places any updates on this web page.

Miscellaneous To the extent permitted by law, you agree not to bring, join, or participate in any class action as to any claim, dispute, or controversy you may have against ConversionSquared or its employees, officers, directors, assignees, and servicers. You agree to the entry of injunctive relief to stop such a lawsuit or to remove yourself as a participant in the suit. This agreement is not a waiver of any of your rights and remedies to pursue a claim individually and not as a class action in binding arbitration as provided above.

This agreement not to bring or participate in class action suits is an independent agreement and shall survive the end of your membership.

To contact us If you have further questions or concerns regarding our privacy practices and our use of your personal data, please send an email to [request@conversionsquared.com](mailto:request@conversionsquared.com) or contact us at our address here:

ConversionSquared Corporation

ATTN: Data Protection Officer,

15851 Dallas Parkway, Suite 600

Addison, TX 75001
